If you have a hundred percent cashless statement for ACL surgery from your health insurance, whether
health insurance covers ACL surgery
or not, friends, this
question is asked a lot, whatever questions I get, that is why
I subscribe to the question, is the internal pressure fiber tap operation
covered by health insurance or not, then friends, it is
definitely a hundred percent cashless
treatment, friends, if you have a
hundred percent cashless statement for ACL surgery from your health insurance,
and friends, there are two-three very
important things to keep in mind in this, you should
watch this video so that you will know
how your ACL surgery can be
covered by health insurance, the
first thing is that
any soft tissue surgery which is done
with a telescope in orthopedics, whose
Naresh
Pimple should be covered, this is the purchase of surgery
in Ankle, ligament surgery,
m-seal m-seal surgery, patella
dislocation surgery, friends, all these
surgeries are
cashless in health insurance, but
for this, one very important thing is that
your health insurance  It should be 2 years old
Hello friends, if you have a 2 year old health
insurance and you
file a claim for ACL surgery in it, then it will be 100
% cashless.
If your health insurance is less than 2 years old, then there are
very high chances of getting a reaction in it, in
fact there are 100
% chances because all the
health insurance companies have a
lock-in period of 2 years, after that you
can get this serial serial serial serial shoulder distraction service done,
you should not get it done before that, there are
some actions in it friends,
as many people say that when our
Haldi Surya Dev ji has said that if it is
excellent then it will be covered, we also have
only two or three months in two years, to some extent
this is true, so friends, this is absolutely true, but
one very important thing to keep in mind is
that if you have had an accident, then
what proof do you have that you have had an
accident and you are not saying anything wrong,
if you have proof of the accident then it is
possible that your health insurance will cover this thing which  We will
cover it friends, there are
only two proofs of accident in India,
first is MLC and second is FIR police, if
you have these two documents in which it is
written that you have met with an accident and
you have got a knee injury in that accident due to which
your seal is broken then
your enemies can cover it, so
friends it is very important that all our
players, whatever their thing,
must get their health insurance done because
after the break, if you friends now get health
insurance and then the
company will cover your surgery, so friends, it is very difficult for you to wait for two years,
hence it is not good to wait,
I will not give you any
other such proof if you do not subscribe for 2 years
and the original copy of which is
written that your knee got injured
during that accident,
friends if you have any such doubt
or you have such laxity in our
PCM serial bank, then you can WhatsApp us
your WhatsApp
number in the link below and we will
give you a free opinion which is the best  Treatment will be done
for you and whether it is
covered in your injury policy or not, you
can sell your college car,
you can take health insurance from any company
friends and if you do
not have health insurance then friends we
also provide these facilities, if ever you feel
that surgery is very expensive or you are
not able to afford it then friends you
can contact us and through this mike we can get
your surgery done at very cheap rates
[Music] do it do it
[Music]
do it